https://www.housingwire.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
HW Media, LLC Privacy Policy – Last updated April 2020
This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices for HW Media, LLC and all of its various platforms and services, and to any services that display this notice. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to “HousingWire” include HousingWire.com, HousingWire email newsletters, the HousingWire audience extension network and HousingWire Magazine.
This notice was updated in January 2020 to reflect GDPR and CCPA compliance standards.
We collect your data (specifically outlined below, but generally basic information about you in a professional context, such as email, job title, company name, etc) strictly to provide you with access to our news, events, and other programs. We will not share this data with anyone unless you explicitly consent to us doing so. We honor your right to privacy and will comply with your wishes to remove your data from our systems.
What data do we collect?
Across our web platforms and events, you will be presented with the opportunity to sign up for newsletters and contests/sweepstakes, purchase magazine subscriptions, purchase event passes, submit your information to access content such as white papers or webinars, apply for eligibility for certain events or awards programs, and more.
The type of information collected generally includes but is not limited to:
Email addressNameJob title or seniorityJob functionIndustry segmentLocationCompany nameMailing/billing addressCredit/debit card information*
*NOTE: we do not save or store this information, and it will only be shared with our payment processors in order to complete the transaction in which you are engaging.
Based on the information you provide to us, we may create or append other information to your profile in the interest of better serving you (for example, your interests). As is the case with all data we collect, this will be kept private and for our business purposes only.
How do we use the information about you?
We use the data you provide to us for the following purposes:
Provide you with access to the content and events we produce.Analyze profile or behavioral data to help us improve the products or recommendations we offer to you.Deliver targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites.In specific cases we will be contractually obligated to share your data with one of our third-party advertisers or partners (for example, webinars, downloads, or special events). You will always have the option to not have your data shared by not taking part in that specific program.
We will store this information to keep you informed about other relevant products that may be useful to you.
We will never use or share the information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.
Some information, such as IP and your email address, may be shared with the following third parties who help us run our website, content and analytics programs. They will only use this information to serve our needs and are prohibited from using it in any other instance. They are:
Google — ad serving and website trackingAddaptive — data management platform and website trackingParse.ly — analytics and website trackingBounceX — forms, email and website trackingHubSpot— data processor, forms, email, and website trackingLinkedIn Insight — campaign reportingFacebook — campaign reportingQuantcast Measure — website trackingAdRoll — data management platform and website tracking
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
Is my data private?
Data is collected or submitted on HW Media’s websites and related platforms, including HousingWire.com, HW Marketing Solutions, and related marketing sites and landing pages. This data is stored in secured databases and is primarily viewed and analyzed in aggregate. It is also used primarily for internal use, with the exception of specific cases which we are contractually obligated to share your data with one of our third-party advertisers or partners (for example, webinars, downloads, or special events). In these instances, we will make it clear that the data you share will be transferred to the third party. You will always have the option to not have your data shared by not taking part in that specific program.
What if I don’t consent?
Consenting to allow us to process and store your data is optional. However, failure to provide that consent will prevent us from delivering the content, events, and other experiences to you as mentioned above.
What if I want you to delete my data?
If you would like to unsubscribe from our communications at any time, you may do so in the footer of any of our emails. If you would like us to delete your information entirely, or request the removal of any information we store about you, please click the link below and enter your email address on the form. Otherwise, by continuing to interact with our emails and programs, you provide us with permission to manage and use your data as described above.
Data Removal Request Form
How safe is my data?
To prevent unauthorized parties from accessing your data and maintain the accuracy and cleanliness of our own data while ensuring the correct use of it, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Questions about our privacy policy or how we use data? Email Operations
Other privacy concerns?
Children’s Guidelines/ COPPA Compliance
HW Media and its related properties are geared to and focused on information for adults and business professionals. HousingWire does not knowingly collect or store any personal information about users under the age of 18.
Log In
Email
